lucidagency.com 2019-07-04

# Privacy Policy - Lucid Agency

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) governs the manner in which Lucid Agency, LLC (“Lucid Agency” “we” “us” “our”) collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the <https://lucidagency.com/> website (“Site”). This Policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Lucid Agency. By accessing the site, utilizing any of the services and/or registering with us, you signify that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by this Policy.

**Personal identification information**  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features, or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously without submitting personally identifiable information to us. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identifying information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance the User experience. A web browser (or mobile phone browser, tablet browser, etc) may places cookies on the device for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Site users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Google Analytics (and other analytics uses)  
**Google Analytics is used to perform many functions. We use the User-ID feature of Google Analytics to combine behavioral information across devices and sessions (including authenticated and unauthenticated sessions). We have enabled the following Google Analytics Advertising features: Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, and DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. We do not merge information collected through any Google advertising product with individual-level information collected elsewhere by our Service. Learn more about how Google collects and uses data  **[here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)**. To opt out of Google Analytics Advertising Features please use [Google Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). To opt out of Google Analytics entirely please use [this link](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Third Parties  
**Except as otherwise expressly included in this Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to other Users on our Site or on other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We are not responsible for any information we do not collect. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**Protecting Children  
**Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to us. For that reason, Lucid Agency does not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13.

**How we use collected information**  
Lucid Agency collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To personalize user experience._ We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _To improve our Site.  _We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To improve customer service.  _Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * _To administer a content, promotion, survey, or other site feature.  _To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _To send periodic emails.  _The email address Users provide may be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email, in accordance with the CAN-SPAM Act.

**Email Communications  
**We may use your email to deliver newsletter(s), as well as for any other promotional purposes (e.g. announcements or giveaways). Email messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the emails we send you, such usage includes whether the email was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you send an email to us, we will collect your email address and the full content of your email, including attached files, and other information you provide. You may indicate your preference to opt out of receiving promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the email you receive or by contacting us directly at privacy@lucidagency.com and we will opt you out as fast as, or faster than, the amount of time required by applicable laws (we can usually do this within one business day).  Please note, however, that you cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to your engagement with us.

**How we protect your information**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information, and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Personal Information Access, Correction and Deletion  
**You can request access to the personal information we have for you by contacting us as below. We will provide you with a copy of the data that we have for you. We will fulfill your request by sending your copy electronically, unless the request specifies a different method. If you believe that the personal information or personal data that we have about you is incorrect, you can contact us to update it. If at any point you wish for us to delete your personal information or personal data, please contact us at [privacy@lucidagency.com](mailto:privacy@lucidagency.com) or by mail at Lucid Agency, Attn: Privacy, 117 E. 5th Street, Tempe AZ  85281\. For your protection, we only fulfill requests for the personal information associated with the email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before fulfilling your request.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
Lucid Agency has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the “updated date” at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please [contact us.](https://lucidagency.com/contact)

**Last Updated Date**  
This document was last updated on May 29th, 2018.
